nsdl.com 2015-03-19

# NSDL

## Privacy Policy

NSDL is sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet. It is therefore important for you to know how the information we receive from you on the Internet is treated.

You can visit our website on the World Wide Web without declaring who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our Web servers collect the domain names of visitors. We use this information to assemble aggregate information about the visitors to our website, and assist with our systems administration and problem resolution activities. Your accessing our site signifies your unconditional consent to allow the collection of your domain names.

There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and other details. Usually, the personal information we collect is used only by us to respond to your inquiry.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release, use or disclose your information when we believe such release of information is necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable statutory requirement, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety as required or permitted by law.

At times we conduct on-line surveys to better understand the needs and profile of our visitors. When we conduct a survey, we will try (but are not obligated) to let you know how we will use the information at the time we collect information from you on the Internet.

You recognize and understand that there is no compulsion on you to provide us with your personal information and any and all personal information provided by you to us is with your full consent, own volition and desire to provide such personal information.

Further, NSDL Web site may contain links to other sites such as business affiliates and software providers. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites. We are not responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting other sites and such other sites are not governed by this privacy statement. We advise you to read their privacy policies before providing your personal information to such sites.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
